koolmobile.net 2018-01-04

# Privacy Policy | Koolmobile

At our website, the privacy of our visitors is of  _extreme_  importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by our website and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many  — perhaps most –  other Web sites, our website makes use of log files. That’s partly for security, so we can identify any problems before they occur.  The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information  _are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable._

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Our website does  _not  _use cookies. You can also see out [Terms of Use](http://koolmobile.net/terms-of-use/).

**Advertising**

This website is partially funded through our generous sponsors and advertisers. We use as little advertising as we can, and — when it’s necessary —  _only_  to cover our hosting and maintenance expenses. We avoid advertising programs with any privacy risks.  In fact, we avoid advertising, period.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our website and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

**Ads that may appear at our website**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners  _may_  include Google Adsense, Commission Junction, Clickbank, Amazon, and other resources that offer useful products or links that seem to interest our website visitors.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our website send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. That’s used, in part, to identify which country you’re from, and which languages your ads could appear in.

Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Our website has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. However, we urge you to disable cookies on your computer if this is a concern for you. That’s controlled in your browser, usually in the Options tab related to privacy, security, or general settings.

Our website’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**File Links & ** **Tutorials**

Files offered on this website are no property of Koolmobile and are linked for educational purposes only.
